Congratulations — we've reached the end
of the problem-solving course.
I know Emily and I have really enjoyed
this journey with you.
We began by thinking about what problem solving is,
and about the process of making decisions.
We talked about the different approaches to problem solving,
and we spent a lot of time on the
hypothesis-led problem-solving approach:
how we define the problem, how we structure it,
all the way to driving recommendations.
One thing we hope you've taken away from this course is that —
there is a structured approach, but it's less about
going through each of the steps one by one,
and more about how you can apply it for yourself
and for your team's day-to-day.
You've had some opportunities to think about that
throughout the course.
Now, going forward, this is the opportunity to think about
how you apply this Monday morning.
I couldn't agree with Marc more. Congratulations.
This is one of the foundational pillars of what will make you
an even more exceptional leader.
But remember, this is just one of the pieces.
Getting beyond the paper, moving beyond the recommendation —
really thinking about how to keep it simple,
practical and easily executable — these are the core things
you'll need to do to realise the true impact of your problem solving.
Congratulations, have fun,
and get out there and practise.